<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Initio - Free, multipurpose html5 template by GetTemplate</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Initio - Free, multipurpose html5 template by GetTemplate</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Download Cristina&#39;s CV</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/home/downloads/download1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/home/downloads/download1/</guid>
      <description>I invite you to explore my professional background and expertise in more detail by downloading my CV. It provides a comprehensive overview of my skills, experience, and contributions across various sectors, including data analytics, policy evaluation, and consulting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/home/subheader/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/home/subheader/</guid>
      <description>Hello! I&amp;rsquo;m Cristina, a passionate data analyst dedicated to using data to drive meaningful insights and change. My journey has been driven by curiosity, dedication, and a desire to contribute to a more just and equitable world.&#xA;Feel free to explore my work and connect with me to discuss insights, collaborations, or just to share a passion for data-driven solutions!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bilingual Translation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/home/services/service3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/home/services/service3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As a native Spanish speaker and fluent English communicator, I have the ability to translate highly technical documents, reports, and data outputs from English to Spanish and vice versa.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Analytics and Modeling</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/home/services/service2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/home/services/service2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;With a strong foundation in policy analysis, supported by a Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Policy Analysis and a Master’s in Methods for Public Policy Analysis, I bring a robust methodological approach to data analytics.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data visualization</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/home/services/service1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/home/services/service1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I specialize in turning complex data sets into clear, actionable visualizations using tools like Ggplot2, Rmarkdown and Quarto in R, Stremlite in Python, Tableau, and Power BI.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Sectoral Problem Solving</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/home/services/service4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/home/services/service4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My experience spans not only the Mexican and US contexts but also a diverse portfolio of sectors, including education policy evaluation, justice system assessments, and health data analysis.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
